All right. So, when you're wanting to
edit an HTML page, it's helpful to know
the HTML has rules. As long as you
follow those rules, um you will be able
to safely work within the page. Um those
rules enable you to write JavaScript
that interacts with those rules to
change how HTML looks. Um we call those
rules the document object model. Um
breaking that down into its three words,
document references the HTML document.
object um references the fact that
everything on the HTML page can be
represented as a JavaScript object. And
then um model is just that everything is
modeled using JavaScript objects. So
that means that if you could do it to a
JavaScript object like accessing an
attribute, you can probably do it to
something that's on the HTML page. If
you can do it to an object in JavaScript
like updating an attribute, you can
probably do it to something that's part
of the HTML page. We call the document
object module
for short.